{
	"questions": [
		{ "question":"How many minutes does it take sun rays to reach earth?", "answers":["8","3","18"] },
		{ "question":"Which star is at the center of our solar system?", "answers":["Sun","North","Moon"] },
		{ "question":"What is the hottest planet in our solar system?", "answers":["Venus","Jupiter","Mercury"] },
		{ "question":"A small body of ice, rock, and cosmic dust loosely packed together?", "answers":["Comet","Moon","Planet"] },
		{ "question":"The moon completes a cycle every _____ days?", "answers":["27","30","8"] },
		{ "question":"The moon shines its own light?", "answers":["No","Yes","Maybe"] },
		{ "question":"Earth is one Astronomical _____ from the sun?", "answers":["Unit","Measurements","Feet"] },
		{ "question":"What is the largest planet in our solar system?", "answers":["Jupiter","Saturn","The Sun"] },
        { "question":"Do to the planets atmophere,\nwhat colour is Mercury's sky?", "answers":["Black","Red","Gold"] },
        { "question":"What is the brightest star in the solar system?", "answers":["Sirius","North","Vega"] },
        { "question":"What planet is know for its famous big red spot?", "answers":["Jupiter","Saturn","Mars"] },
        { "question":"What is the name of the force that pulls us down to earth?", "answers":["Gravity","The force","Nuclear"] },
        { "question":"Uranus is the _____ planet from the sun?", "answers":["7","8","5"] },
        { "question":"Have people ever stepped foot on mars?", "answers":["No","Yes","Maybe"] },
        { "question": "What is the smallest planet, \nnot counting dwarfs?", "answers": [ "Mercury", "Earth", "Uranus" ] },
        { "question": "The word 'astrophsics' is based on greek words \nwhich of these bodies astro translates to?","answers": [ "Star", "Moon", "Planet" ] },
        { "question": "Which planet is sometimes called Earth sister planet?", "answers": [ "Venus", "Mars", "Neptune" ] },
        { "question": "How many planets in our solar system are made from gas?", "answers": [ "4", "5", "1" ] },
        { "question": "The planet neptune was named for the Roman god of the _____ ?", "answers": [ "Sea", "Zeus", "Cronus" ] },
        { "question": "How many of the planets, apart from Earth, are named after gods?", "answers": [ "All of them", "Two", "Four" ] },
        { "question": "A Nebula is a cloud of _____ and dust?", "answers": [ "Gas", "Paper", "Magic" ]},
        { "question": "Uranus along with Neptune is catagorised as what type of planet?","answers": [ "Ice giants", "Hot lava", "Terrestrial" ] },
        { "question": "Which planet is tilted on its side?", "answers": [ "Uranus", "Saturn", "Earth" ] },
        { "question": "Which of the following is our Solar systems only natural light source?", "answers": [ "A star", "The moon", "Lightbulbs" ] },
        { "question": "The asteroid belt is located between which two planets?", "answers": [ "Jupiter and Mars", "Earth and Mars", "Uranus and Neptune" ] },
        { "question": "The earths axis is slightly titled. \nWhat does this cause?", "answers": [ "Seasons", "Life", "Rocks" ] },
        { "question": "Does Venus take a longer time or shorter time in Earth days to orbit the Sun?","answers": [ "Shorter", "Longer", "The same" ]},
        { "question": "The largest dust storms in the solar system are on which planet?",  "answers": [ "Mars", "Earth", "Venus" ] },
        { "question": "What dwarf planet crosses Neptune's orbit?", "answers": [ "Pluto", "Ceres", "Eris" ]},
        { "question":"When a full moon causes the ocean to rise what force is at work?", "answers":["Gravity","Drag","Magic"] },
        { "question":"What do we call the Sun and all the space objects in orbit around it?", "answers":["Solar System","Universe","Galaxy"] },
        { "question":"How many moons does Jupiter have?", "answers":["79","89","50"] },
        { "question":"Earth _____ the sun?", "answers":["Orbits","Is","Moves"] },
        { "question":"Does every planet have at least one moon?", "answers":["No","Yes","Maybe"] }
	]
}